www.ZooCine.CoM
Watch Movies and Series!
Fuck!
Eylül! (September)
Finally! I was so worried!
You're not answering your calls.
I tried to reach you all night.
Hello? Who am I talking to?
Eylül, are you back in our world?
mall
Couldn't talk yesterday. Didn't
want to bother you with business.
I managed up until yesterday.
But you have to tell them something.
Do I, miss?
What do you think I should say?
It's all ready. They've been
waiting for an answer for a month.
Volkswagen had the network approve it.
By the way he is quite taken by you.
You have to say something.
What will you say, Limey?
Gee! That's what you came up with in a
month. Look, we will have so much fun!
From one end of the world to another.
It is a dream job, girl!
- A Small September Affair.
-Come again?
Name of the show.
- So, you accept?
-Already did. Called as soon as I came.
You serious, girl?
Never.
Let's have the first show at Peru.
Get to know handsome Aztec boys.
Then we go to Rom for...
Too much talk!
I'll come to the channel with
At ll Kurt. Meet you there?
Okay, fine!
Anyway daddy is calling.
Kiss you!
Daddy?
You came, honey?
I did.
Your morn wants to see you.
Maybe a dinner at the club...
Only mom wants to see me,
you don't?
Of course not!
I want to see you more.
Alright then. Order the
pastrami pies. Kiss you!
Today, I feel like playing the
lead in my own movie.
Credits are running and
I am starting my new life.
Don't bother putting me
In your heart
Don't wrap your arms around me,
I can't stay there
Have fun and laugh
Don't talk so bitter
What is life anyway
But a brief meeting
This how I am
This is how I have always been
I don't look back, I refuse tears
I am stronger for my failures
Ma'am! We missed you.
It's on me today.
Don't call me on your path
My path is different
Different are my destinations
Different are my challenges
This how I am
This is how I have always been
I can burn in darkness
I can stand in emptiness
I don't fall
I have wings in my soul
I can go as I come
I can give up love
I have no chains on my neck
Don't bother putting me
In your heart
Don't wrap your arms around me
I can't stay there
Have fun and laugh
Don't talk so bitter
A SMALL SEPTEMBER AFFAIR
Mom, look who's here!
Excuse me, excuse me!
May I have a photograph?
Sure.
Sorry man, can we
have a photograph, too?
Sure, go ahead.
- You want something?
-Yes, you.
Have I done something wrong?
-Yes, very much so.
What is it?
What did I do wrong now, Limey?
You fell in love with me.
And you did not with me?
I am much too joyful to fall in love.
Even if I lose each and every time
I wouldn't feel sorry at all
I wasn't so fragile once
I was beaten
By the enemies I created
- Are you alright?
-I am.
It is a perfect day.
That's more like it.
Welcome back, Eylül.
Today I have everything.
Today everybody loves me.
Today is the first day of my
beautiful, perfect, fabulous life.
Yes,dad?
Where are we?
When they brought me to the
hospital, my heart stopped beating.
Then...
I was unconscious for a week.
They put me in a private clinic.
- Did she wake up?
-No.
Then one day, as my mother
came out of the bathroom...
Look at this paper they put here...
Mom, I am so hungry.
Will you order something?
Eng in! Eng in, she's awake!
Eng in, she'll fall! Eng in, hurry!
Following two days, fully awake,
I did interesting stuff.
You rascal!
Honey, you had an accident, but
don't worry, it is over now. OK?
You are alright.
So they say. And I believe.
- Hey, don't look.
-Miss Talley!
- Are those mine?
-Huh-huh.
Is that your professional opinion?
Everything is fine.
I am fine, right? I'm not crazy.
I don't think so.
May I ask you a few questions?
Sure, go ahead.
- How old are you?
-24.
- I see.
-You see what? My age? 27.
- Marital status?
-Single. But I have plenty of options.
- Your occupation?
-I work at a production company.
But now she will have her own show.
Called, "A Small September Affair".
Wait, I didn't say yes yet.
Crazy girl, you already found a name!
Do you remember the accident?
Do you remember
what you were wearing?
A coral colored top.
And jean shorts.
No, white. White shorts.
Do you remember where you are?
Someplace like a coastal town.
You know, like in the villages...
A coffeehouse shadowed by trees.
You are there too. We are together.
-Where is that place?
You know the place we went.
All’s commercial.
You know... Boadicea!
We have just arrived.
We...
We sat down at a coffeehouse
to have a smoke.
Is that where we had the accident?
Say something, Berra?
That was a month before the accident.
You remember one month ago.
What?
No way, we just, you know...
I don't remember after that.
I don't remember after that!
I don't remember my last month!
- Alright, calm down.
-Calm down how?!
How many times did you die?
How do you know?
Then what? When did we come back?
-We only went for the weekend.
- I had a commercial shooting.
-Easy, we just went...
...for the weekend. And stayed
that long. Then came back.
The rest is same old story.
Everything was normal. Really.
So there is nothing
You're not telling me?
If there were, how can we keep it
from you? You'd find out.
Yes, I would. And beat the crap
out of you. Starting with you.
Okay.
Don't worry, your memory
will come back real soon.
- It will, right?
-It will.
It will. So...
So I'm okay.
Everything is fine.
Get well soon.
I stayed in the hospital
for another week.
Picked up two doctors,
scorned a nurse, stole a purse.
Then I signed some papers and
took over my life where I left.
Everyone told me I am fine so much,
eventually I believed them.
Limey, since you are up,
why don't you grab me a beer.
I'll get it.
What's up with you?
Guys, Limey is bringing me a beer.
Bravo! Grab me a beer, boy!
Since you are there,
fetch some wine, too.
- What else? Shall I open it?
-Open, open.
Elul?
Elul!
- Let me g!
-Eylül, easy!
Let me go, I have to figure it out!
Easy! Okay!
I have to go!
- Eyeful, okay! Eylül, it's alright!
-Eylül! Easy!
- Easy! Eylül, calm down!
-Get back. It's alright, get back!
'EYRIE! Gulley
-Easy!
Alright.
-it's okay... We are here.
Look at me, look at me!
It's okay, honey.
- Poor girl...
-She just couldn't recover.
- Berra, what's happening to me?
-it's alright, honey. It's over.
- What's happening?
-You got a little confused.
- I have to go somewhere.
-Where, honey?
I don't know. I don't know...
- Here's your coffee.
-Come...
Eylül, it will be alright. This is
all so normal, you almost died.
We are all here for you. I am here.
Everything is alright now.
- It is, right?
-it is.
Everything is alright, Eylül.
Everyone is fine.
But if everyone is fine,
why do you feel so incomplete?
Incomplete... It lacks sugar.
No, really, it lacks sugar.
Welcome back, Talley!
Move!
- And a biscuit.
-As you order, my lady.
Berra...
The other day,
I noticed something weird.
What?
I have no texts on my phone
from the last month.
So?
A whole month...
No one tested me?
Because you lost your phone.
Your battery died and they got
deleted, or someone deleted them.
You know it was lost.
That is my phone.
-August 4, "Eylül, are you OK?"
Eylül, will you give me that?
August 7, "Limey, come back,
this has gone too far."
Eylül, don't read, please!
August 30, "Don't be afraid, we are
coming. Get out of that house ASAP."
- Eylül! Stop...
-What house?
A day before the accident.
What house?
-it's all over, we are all fine!
No, we are not! We are not fine!
What happened to me?
What house, tell me! Where was I?
Tell me the truth, Berra. The truth.
You were at Boadicea.
- Why?
-How would I know! You wanted to stay.
- With whom?
-No one.
You got drunk at a bar,
called me to come and get you.
So I tested that we are coming.
Then we came and got you, that's all.
- So I didn't meet anyone there?
-No! No one!
I stayed here for a month?
Doesn't look like much from up above.
- Airport is gone! It's sea all over!
-This is a seaplane.
Fuck you Eylül.
Fuck my friendship.
Fuck my life!
Hey! You're changing
the plane's balance!
I took Berra and came to
this bizarre island.
They are hiding something from me.
But I don't know what.
Our hotel is right after that turn.
Gelling Hotel. I feel so dirty.
Shot gun. I go first.
Fine, alright.
But be quick, I am freezing.
That face...
What is it?
- I'll buy some toothpaste. You go.
-What?
Bully some toothpaste and come.
You go.
Okay, fine.
Sisyphus...
Where did we meet?
Why was I here for a month?
-Hello.
Do I know you?
It's me... Lone.
Couldn't recognize you.
What do you want?
Is this a game?
What game?
- Come on, let's go home.
-What home? What home?!
- Eyeful...
-How do you know my name?
- You don't remember?
-Don't remember what?
Don't remember what?
That you are in love with me...
My name is Lone.
I lived alone on an island.
I draw for a living.
But a month ago something happened.
- One eggplant coffee, one orange tea.
-Sure.
Lone! What is this, man?
Are my eyebrows like this?
Alright, man, we'll figure it out.
They will settle down when it dries.
Settle it, man. Do whatever
you will, make it right.
- Barrack? Barrack!
-Huh, honey?
- Coffee, tea, cigarettes, something?
-Fine.
- Let's sit?
-See you, girls. We will come.
My head is killing me.
What kind of a wind is this?
I am going to the hotel,
I am awfully tired.
I'll rest and call you when I wake up.
-Okay, call when you wake up.
- I got your bag.
-Alright, thanks.
Bye, honey!
No, Eylül! Will you read
newspapers on our trip'?
- No, I am not reading the paper.
-What are you doing then?
Weekly caricature.
You know "Crazy Durum"...
He's this old man who lives on
an island. Really carefree dude.
To every problem, he says:
"No worries, we'll deal with it.”
- Who'? Who's the artist?
-Te kin something...
My idol. The man I will marry.
Let me see.
Hello. My name is Lone.
"Te“ (Lone) of Te kin.
Those caricatures,
I draw them.
You say we marry,
no worries, we'll deal with it.
- Will you order coffee?
-Yes, let's.
- You buying?
-I'm buying.
Excuse me. Can we get one of those,
you know the specialty here...
- Eggplant coffee?
-Yes, exactly. Two please.
Anybody?
Berra?
You left me alone for a moment
and the things I went through!
I almost got kidnapped.
They wanted your number for
ransom. Of course I didn't give it.
Will you listen to me a moment?
Berra?
Have a commercial break or something.
Stop bickering, At ll!
What should I have done?
She would have come
alone anyway.
No, she doesn't
remember anything.
Don't be ridiculous,
we won't go to Lane's.
We'll have eggplant pie
and come back.
Don't worry.
I am with her all the time.
I said don't worry...
-I'm back!
Limey is back.
I got to go. Bye.
- What's up?
-At ll Kurt called.
- What's he saying?
-Busting my balls.
What did you do?
Did you remember something?
Come, Sisyphus, come boy.
Come.
She doesn't remember me.
It's my fault. Foolish me!
I shouldn't have introduced you.
The sign is good, man.
No need for this.
That's not enough for me.
it has to be perfect.
Alright then.
- No way.
-Huh?
No way if you keep
staring stupidly from a far.
You go build yourself a sand castle.
You are an intelligent man, Lone.
But you know nothing
about these matters.
Go be with your parents a little.
You know what you need, Lone?
- Another face?
-A matchmaker child.
Don't... Don't! Guiana
Gilgamesh is my best friend on the island.
She sells hats on the beach...
...gives advices to everyone,
and gets me in a lot of trouble.
A gentleman sent this to you.
He said...
Who...
So?
She asks if you know a
good place for dinner.
Well... There is the "Sinking Fish".
She can go there. It's a nice place.
She doesn't mean that!
She says take me there.
- She really said so?
-Go ask yourself.
Ugly people, to be noticed
by beautiful people...
. . . do unexpected things.
We are so used to being invisible...
...that an ugly person, with just a
glance, can fall desperately in love.
What's it got to do with it?
Berra? Who is Lone?
- What?
-Lone.
I remember that name. Wears a funny
t-shirt, has paint on his hands.
You mean the painter boy.
What about him?
- Who is he?
-No one. Well... I'll tell you.
We came here. Went to the beach on
the second day. We were just chatting.
Then a little girl came to you.
A gentleman sent this to you.
He said...
What did he say?
It can't make you any
more beautiful, but...
- But?
-it will protect you from the sun.
Nicely said. Who is this poet?
Really...
Will you pass on a message from me?
What is it?
Does he know a nice
place for dinner?
- What are you saying?
-We have a guest for dinner.
What did you do, Limey?
I'm tired of this
wasteland of an island!
We'll have some fun, some action.
I'll hold his hand,
it'll make him happy.
It will be funny, we'll have fun.
-Girl, you are so bad!
Do you remember?
I just have a feeling.
What kind of a feeling?
Different...
Fun...
If it is so fun, dear Eylül...
...why are they so afraid
you will remember?
- I'll go buy cigarettes.
-Don't, they'll buy for us.
No need, I'll be back in a minute.
Is there a place called the
"Blinking Fish" here?
- Sinking Fish? There.
-Thanks.
I had an accident. Look...
I don't remember you.
The day we were to meet here...
I came early and
made preparations.
May I have a lighter?
Preparations?
No, mom, I am not home.
Just called so you won't worry.
I will meet a friend for dinner.
Yes, a girl.
She saw my drawings and liked them.
She wanted to meet me.
Okay. If we hit it off,
I'll let you know.
Okay. I will ask if she knows a second
language. Okay, mom, I got to go.
Alright, kisses.
Mom... She is so beautiful.
Thanks.
-You're welcome.
There is just this, mom.
I am scared.
Because I am not like them.
The fish smell on my hands,
it doesn't come off.
My armpits sweat faster than theirs.
I am on foreign territory, morn.
That's why I am scared.
Mine, did you put
soap wort in this?
- I told them to, Te kin.
-You told. Where is my wine?
- Here.
-You waited it in cold water?
I did that, too.
Lone, I am here, here for you.
Look, everything is fine. Okay?
No worries, we'll deal with it.
-We will.
Lone, may I have my hand back?
She is here.
I am scared, mom.
Because this girl will hurt me.
And then forget me.
Good, there are others, too.
I was afraid you'd be alone.
This is our last night.
They planned a party on the beach.
I said, I have a date, but they busted
my balls, I couldn't get out of it.
Would you mind?
Appetizers look splendid.
I am off.
But all I can think of...
She kissed me.
I am sorry.
You remember?
No worries, we'll deal with it.
Don't answer, please don't!
Hello?
Eyeful, where are you?
You went for cigarettes and poof!
-I am at "Stinking Fish”.
It's not "Stinking" you fool!
"Sinking Fish” Are you alone?
- I am with Lone.
-No...
Eylül, get out of there right now!
Why?
Sylvie, get out!
We are just talking.
Eylül, do as I say!
Leave there now and come here!
Why? Why? Tell me already!
Tell me what happened!
- Don't listen... Not yet.
- Don't come closer! Don't... Don't...
Berra, something bad
happened here, right?
- Yes, honey.
-What happened? What?
The last day... On your last day here,
you called us and said something...
Do you remember?
-No.
Try to remember.
What did you say to me?
What did I say?
You said, "Berra, I am so
scared. Come and get me."
I am scared...
I am scared... I am scared...
Did he do something to me?
Did he?
Where are you, did you leave?
Berra... Berra, come and get me.
Come and get me out of here.
Okay, honey. I'm coming.
Eylül, wait! Lillie!
Go!
Anybody?
Anybody? Help!
Help! Anybody?
Don't come closer...
Eylül, it's me...
Would I ever hurt you?
Don't come closer! Go away!
- I am Lone.
-Don't come closer... Don't...
Limey, you know me better than
anyone else. Don't you remember?
You did something bad to me. I...
Let me go. Please leave, please!
Make your hand a fist.
Make a fist!
Elul!
Berra!
Please...
Remember me.
Why? Why do you want me
to remember?
Because those memories
are not just yours, Eylül.
Elul!
Berra, what did that guy do to me?
Don't think about it now. Sleep,
rest. We'll talk in the morning. Okay?
I did not stay at Sinking Fish
that night. We went to the beach.
- What? Do you remember?
-Lone told me. Then what?
Then it was morning.
We packed to return.
Elul!
Do not linger, come on.
Alright. We will get
Eylül and come.
Elul!
Come on, the shuttle is leaving.
We are waiting for you.
You go. I'll stay here.
What's going on?
I'm not coming with you.
You won't come with me?
Why?
Is there someone else?
What's that got to do with it?
I am bored.
-Bored...
Bored of what?
-Us.
If you are bored of us,
why did you come here with me?
Don't laugh, it's not funny.
He cried and begged all the way,
smothered me. So boring!
I am not laughing at that.
What are you laughing at?
Because finally I am
starting to remember.
Sister Lillie! Sister Cancan
prepared jams for breakfast.
Cancan is a man's name.
Who is she?
Lone knows the place,
he'll take you there.
I am...
I am waiting at the coffeehouse!
Alright, don't get angry about it!
Don't Eylül, it is better
to forget some things.
Give up before it's too late.
It is dangerous
to remember some things.
Don't, you foolish girl.
I'm off to the beach.
Come when you wake up.
I'll make it clear from the start,
I don't know you, I don't trust you.
One mistake and
I'll give you the black eye.
- Black eye?
-I know kick box.
Last day before returning to
Istanbul, what happened to me?
I'll tell you, but on one condition.
I'll tell it step by step.
Starting from the first day.
Or I won't tell you.
You have 24 hours.
Two teas please. Start.
Waiter... Waiter?
Waiter...
He is not a waiter! Child worker!
What happened to my tea?
- Coming, ma'am.
-Come on now, it's been half an hour.
To begin with; I don't like jam,
I don't eat eggs, white bread never.
- Come.
-Where?
Poppy, mint...
I don't know this one.
Besom, it is nice.
Grape, strawberry, pear...
-Pillows, shoes...
They jammed anything they find.
-Yes.
Why?
Tomato...
Tomato.
This is so good!
Close the drapes,
don't let anyone in.
You have a stain, what did you...
-Bee.
Bee!
You did not come near me
again that day.
You were leaving the next day.
You said goodbye at the coffeehouse.
Good bye.
Good bye?
There is the vintage.
-Come again?
Well, we islanders gather.
And harvest grapes.
Something we do once a year.
So of course you...
I mean you cannot...
You cannot go back today. Don't.
I am leaving.
Don't make me eat anything else.
You know there are wind turbines
on the other end of the island?
They say if you watch the sunset over
there, you don't fear death anymore.
- Who says that?
-Cuttle Fish Mahomet. Good fisherman.
Half crazy.
This is the last one.
Okay.
- Bob appetite.
-Eggplant pie.
OK.
- Tea?
-No, coffee.
Two coffees.
Lone!
Come here, it is so
beautiful from here!
- No, I am good.
-Come, let's take a photo.
I'll put it on pentagram.
Come...
Come, come.
Sit.
You take it. Get the back,
your car. Everything.
Look, wait, you press here...
What are you doing? Give it back.
Give it back. It's my phone!
Make the frame. Come on.
Make the frame... Okay.
Now close one eye and
close the diaphragm a little.
What do I do?
Close one eye and close
the diaphragm a little.
Okay.
Take the photo you see.
Close your eyes.
Develop the picture
with your eyes closed.
- How's that?
-Remember.
Enough!Enough H.
You're not telling the truth.
Tell me the truth.
- I am.
-Tell the truth!
Mall
I wouldn't do any of
those things you said.
I wouldn't hold your hand at sunset!
No, I am not lying.
Look at yourself and look at me, Lone.
What would someone like me...
...have to do with someone like you?
-But it happened. You held my hand.
You chose me.
-Why would I choose you?
I don't know.
If I knew what I did,
wouldn't I do it again?
Was it something I did or said?
If only I knew...
I really don't know what to
say to you now, how to be.
Eylül...
How do we repeat a miracle?
I really don't know.
Maybe nothing happened then either.
Maybe you just imagined it all.
Don't answer. Let's go to
one last place, please.
At ll, get in your car and
come here right away!
Did something happen to Eylül?
I don't know where she is.
Her phone is off.
Berra?
What have I done, At ll?
Why did I bring her here?
You know the day we flied kite...
You don't believe him, Eylül.
Then why do you still listen to him?
Out of pity?
Or are you beginning to like his story,
the girl in his story?
The next day you came to the
coffeehouse without a bag.
You said you wanted to
go for a swim.
I said, no worries,
we'll deal with it.
- Where is this place?
-Don't you want to go for a swim?
There are only hills here.
Wait a minute, wait. Stop!
Oh my, it is all prickles. Slow down.
-Want to bet on something?
God! I love bets.
Can you manage not to
speak for two hours?
What kind of a bet is that?
That's plain torture!
- Then I win.
-What?! Hell you do!
You don't even talk to me.
That's how you are. Am I like that?
I earn my living by talking.
-I win.
Like hell you win!
We did not bet on it yet.
I become pretty wild when I don't
talk. You wouldn't want to see that.
- I win!
-I cannot not talk!
If I win...
Tonight you will go out with me...
-OK?
And dance.
I don't want to.
- You don't know how to swim, right?
-Nonsense, I don't have a bathing suit.
You live on an island,
but don't know how to swim?
You don't talk to people.
You don't mingle in crowds.
You don't dance. You don't swim.
-I am happy the way I am.
You don't want to see the world?
I mean...
Don't you want to get drunk,
dance, sing and shout?
Don't you want to
live a little, Lone?
Wanting is not enough, Elul.
Not everyone is as lucky as you.
Come on, don't give me
that loser story.
I am scared, alright?
Scared of everything, everyone!
I am scared!
Are you happy now?
Come...
Eylül, I can't.
You don't have to do anything.
Just come after me.
Eylül...
Trust me.
Come...
Eylül...
Don't be scared, I am here.
I will hold you. Come...
- I am going back.
-Wait!
Don't you want to come to me?
Come towards me.
I will hold you. Don't be scared.
Come...
Okay... Alright.
- Nothing to be scared of, right?
-There' a lot to be scared of.
But I am not scared anymore.
Do you remember?
You kept complaining...
I am allergic to everything,
I can't sing, I can't dance.
Eylül, I am Lone.
Please remember me.
When you came out of the sea...
...you drew something there.
And I said the waves
will wipe it away.
Elul?
What you wrote...
it will be lost and gone.
It won't be. Waves will take it
with them, and wherever you go...
...they will leave it
on its shore for you.
tektite LOVES ELUL
- Lone!
-Eylül...
I missed you so much.
I only remember that day.
- We don't have much time.
-For what? Time for what?
The next day...
I remember.
Come on, shake it a little.
Shake it.
You are a dreamer. You must have
dreamt about this. Tell me the truth.
I did. I did, but...
If you could see the man in my dreams,
you would be crazy about him.
Close your eyes.
- Eyeful...
-Come on close!
Now dance with me in your mind.
- How?
-Like this.
One day an ugly man fell in
love with a beautiful girl.
And the beautiful girl
started to play with him.
- Is it alright?
-Yes Super.
The girl did what
she knew best to him.
Holding and letting him go.
Inflicting small tortures
and then calling him back.
Making fun of him a little,
yet staying with him.
Do you have a spare bed at home?
Yes.
The girl who does not know,
recognize or believe in love...
...that night embarked on a journey
to the heart of the ugly man.
- Is this your place?
-Mother's.
Of course!
Do you make these?
What are they?
Where do you find them?
It's driftwood.
I pick them up from the sea.
Who is that, your mother?
- Who?
-That.
- No, it's me.
-You?
Don't these hit your head?
-Well..
You want a drink?
-You will give me a drink?
Come one then. Give me a drink.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
Is this a medieval torture device?
What the hell is this?
Torture device?
No, it helps make thread from wool.
- You have wool? Let's make thread.
-Look...
Look, this is my bathtub.
I shower here,
but nobody can see anything.
And this is where
I work with driftwood.
And that's my toilet.
And this is my bed.
-Your bed?
Yes, my bed.
What's in there?
Do you take young girls here and...
You are him!
You are Crazy Durum!
Are you the man I am to marry?
The man in my dreams was so...
I didn't mean that.
There is a small September affair.
And I can't deal with it...
Go home now.
Because if you don't go now,
you will never want to go.
Hi.
Here. Draw me.
-Why?
I want to see what you see.
I remember.
It's like a question I haven't studied
for and I am trying to answer it.
I am confused. I'm shabby.
No one's stopping me.
I am going somewhere
I have never been to.
What are you doing?
Looking at you.
Other people tell us who we are.
From a man stranded on an island...
...I'm listening to my story
told most beautifully.
Admit it Eylül,
you missed me, didn't you?
l...
Hello, Eyeball?
Hello?
Hello, Barrack?
Eyeful, where are you?
Is that you?
Yes, it is me.
Who else could it be, you idiot?
I thought I heard someone.
No, I was sleeping, you woke me up.
Really? Sorry. What are you doing?
Who is with you? Are you out?
Who is that?
Nobody, Berra!
There is no one.
Come back then.
You've taken so long all alone.
I had a lot to drink. I'll get some
sleep and call you back. Alright?
Okay, get your sleep,
then get a ticket. OK?
Okay, I'll be back.
I am begging to get suspicious!
I was going to turn off the ringer.
I'll go do some work.
Lone?
Lone? Look, a shooting star.
-Make a wish.
I did. Shall I tell you what?
- So did I.
-What is it?
What?
I wished I was someone else.
Someone tough and handsome.
When you look at him,
the world stops spinning.
Someone who can let out his feelings
like a bullet shot.
He'll be mad at you, he'll say:
I am not 'nobody,' I am Te kin Bullet.
Someone who would hold you by the
hand and, pull you by his side.
And say, "I don't want you to go,
I forbid you to go.
Now that I found you
I'll never let you go."
But I am not like that, Eylül.
Whatever I do...
...I can only be me. Lone.
I want the man with paint
on his hands. I want you.
I was so happy here.
What else?
I can't stop, Lone.
If I stop, I sink down, but...
With you I stood without sinking.
Like...
-Like what?
Love...
Is this love?
It can't be, can it?
I mean love... I mean, it is...
If you need to ask, it is not.
But it does not matter, right?
It does not matter.
We have so much time anyway.
Right?
Sure we do.
You will cook me many more meals.
I will.
I will nag at you so much more.
Elul!
Don't you go anywhere.
Come, come, I will
introduce you to someone!
Where are you going?
-Come home.
- You will be there, right?
-I will be waiting for you.
At the end of the story...
Nothing bad happens, right?
Lillie! Limey, I was so scared!
You got it all wrong.
Come on now, let's go to Lane's.
You can't! You can't.
Lone told me everything,
I remember everything now.
- Everything?
-Yes, everything.
Berra, you don't understand.
I spent a wonderful month here.
Nothing bad happened on that last
night. it was all like a dream.
- Then? Do you remember the morning?
-I don't need to! Don't need to!
Everything is alright, it's all fine.
-No, honey!
Everything is not alright.
Limey, try to remember, please.
I don't want to. It's all fine.
I don't want to remember.
It's all fine, everything is alright!
-Eylül...
Nothing bad happened.
Limey, master of cruel love...
...loving life more than people,
finally surrendered.
- Where to?
-I'll prepare breakfast.
- You? For me?
-What? You don't believe me?
Good grief! I will prepare you
a breakfast so good that...
...the whole island will come running
and circle around you. You'll see.
Nothing bad happened.
That was the happiest day of my life.
I can stand in emptiness
I don't fall
I have wings in my soul
I can go as I come
I can give up love
I have no chains on my neck
Don't bother putting me
In your heart
Don't wrap your arms around me
I can't stay there
Have fun and laugh
Don't talk so bitter
What is life anyway
But a brief meeting
This how I am
This is how I have always been
I can burn in darkness
I can stand in emptiness
I don't fall
I have wings on my soul
I can go as I come
I can give up love
I have no chains on my neck
Don't bother putting me
In your heart
Don't wrap your arms around me
I can't stay there
I remember now.
How scared I felt
looking at that girl in the mirror...
How fear has conquered love...
I remember.
Hello, Eyeball?
Hi, Berra,
can you come and get me?
jellylike, where are you?
Are you alright? Eylül!
I'm not alright.
I'm scared. I'm scared...
I ran... Ran away!
I left Lone there.
Went back to the hotel.
-Then we came.
You told us that there was someone.
-Someone hitting on me, I said.
I was scared of him, I said.
-We were to leave in the morning.
Three of us went to a bar.
Eylül, please remember, please...
I do not like this.
I don't want to remember anymore.
Come on!
Guys, we have only one night.
So we party for two nights, alright?
- Five! Come on!
-Our girl is so bored, man.
Then tomorrow we make a boat trip.
See all the bays around here
and then return to Istanbul.
Killer idea!
Let's do that, please!
Hi.
- Hi.
-You forgot this.
Berra, At ll...
Lone.
-Hi, man.
Hi.
What's up, man? On vacation?
How long have you been here?
-It's been eight years.
-Lone lives on the island.
- Maybe Eylül will come more often, too.
-I don't think so.
Some jerks have been
hitting on her,here.
She's had enough of the place.
-Maybe she'll come back for me.
She is my girlfriend...
Lone is the funniest man
on the island!
- Apparently.
-That's obvious.
- What do you do, man?
-I am a painter. I paint signs.
Sign painter.
How did you meet this lunatic?
I just took a look at her,
and fell in love at first sight.
Then I invited her to dinner.
She stood me up, I ate alone.
I didn't know how to swim,
she taught me.
I can't dance either.
She said dance, I did.
Then she came to my place.
We cooked, made wine.
Looked at each other not speaking.
Shut the whole world out,
leaving only the two of us.
We made love.
Lovechild.
-What are you talking about?
- Like hell!
-Is that the man who hit on you?
- You come over here!
-At ll! At ll, wait!
I'm really fed up with this place.
Come on, let's go.
Eylül, what is he doing?
- Wait, I'll take care of it.
-Don't mock the guy.
- Lone, you're embarrassing yourself.
-Eylül...
It's over. We are going
back tomorrow morning.
We had a wonderful month,
but it's over.
What did you expect?
-I'll do whatever you want.
I'll be the man you want.
Please come home.
What did I tell you, Lone?
Do not trust me,
do not get used to me.
This is how I am.
-But you too...
Don't come after me.
I left him like that.
I left him and walked away.
Let me go! Let me go!
I have to go somewhere!
- Jellylike! Enough. You are not well.
-What do you mean I am not well?
After the accident...
You did not recover completely.
- What happened to me?
-jellylike, we called the hospital.
- The hospital?
-They are waiting for you.
You'll be fine there.
-What happened to me?!
Limey, we have to go.
Please don't be like this!
Come on, let's go.
They are waiting for us.
Elul!
'Evolute
Take back your gift, Lone.
I did not like your gift.
Eylül, wait! Limey, stoup
Ditto .
OPE" up, Elul!
I did not like
this memory, this girl.
I miss the story you told.
Take me back there. Please...
Guiana Gilligan...
Where is Lone?
-Here!
What do you mean here?
Where is Lone?
Right here!
Do you finally remember
everything, Eylül?
What is it?
Hello. It's me, Lone.
Do I know you?
I couldn't remember...
What do you want?
No, no...
Two teas, please.
No,no,no“.
Anybody?
Help me! Help me!
Don't come closer...
Elul!
Lone... Lone...
Lone! I was so scared!
I was so scared, Lone!
Lone, I thought I was
going insane! Lone!
Lone... Lone, where?
Lone!
Now you know, Eylül.
You don't deserve a second chance.
You are only watching the end
of a story already told.
Eylül...
That's enough, Lone.
Give up on me.
Limey, come on, the plane will leave.
Send him away or I'll...
Alright, calm down.
Just a minute.
Get a hold of yourself.
Don't be so weak.
That's not why I came.
Why then?
To hear you say just once.
- Say what?
-That you are in love with me.
At least let me know that it is true.
-You got it all wrong.
This is not love!
You're lying.
With me you came out in public,
found someone to talk to.
With me, instead of staying home
dreaming, you lived a little.
You are not in love with me, Lone.
You just need me.
Eylül...
You are a coward
imprisoned to this island.
You can't come where I am going.
Forget me.
I am much too joyful to fall in love.
Lone... Lone, look, I am back.
See, I came back.
Lone... Lone, I am here.
Look here. Lone... Lone!
Lone, come on, let's go home.
Look, I am here.
Lone. . . Lone
Lone!
Nothing to be scared of, right?
-There's a lot to be scared of.
But I am not scared anymore.
I am not scared anymore...
Lone, stop!
Wait, stop!
Lone!
I am here!
I will save you!
Lone!
A PAINFUL LOSS
Our condolences for the tragic
loss of our colleague TE KIN BULLET.
No! Stop! Lone!
You got to stop! No!
I am sorry... I am sorry...
I am sorry...
What you wrote will be lost.
It won't be. Waves will
take it with them...
...and wherever you go, they will
leave it on its shore for you.
ELUL LOVES tektite (LONE)
THERE WAS A SMALL AFFAIR
I COULDN'T DEAL WITH IT.
telekinetic BULLET
1985-2013
"For my wife Mar, who made me
live a miracle again."
A SMALL SEPTEMBER AFFAIR
www.ZooCine.CoM
Watch Movies and Series!